thanks to YouTube and Eurosport for
sponsoring this short I wanted to know
if Olympic medal winners drink any
alcohol any alcohol no no alcohol only
water sometimes uh sometimes something
with sugar but alcohol is bad for sports
it's like to eat a lot of sugars but for
sports when you arrive at high level
like that you need to be perfect all the
time um honestly no not really like I
might have a sip of champagne to
celebrate but you know not a big drinker
no no no you know it's uh I need to take
care of my weight and uh so it's alcohol
is not really like fitting with my
lifestyle great thank you very much I'll
have a full video out this week with
more interviews with Meda winners
including rugby 7's gold medalist Andy
teimo so stay tuned